Finding Aid to the Dee Mosbacher papers and Woman Vision records SSC.MS.00740
Sophia Smith Collection
- Woman Vision records, 1950-2014; 1984-2013; 2; 61.28 linear feet (97 boxes)
  - All God's Children, 1992-2007
    - Tape logs and audiovisual materials, 1992-1996; 8 boxes (Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38)
      - Computer files for production of All God's Children, 1992-1997; .0033 Gigabytes (6 E01 disk images from 6 floppy disks)
        This born-digital material is not currently available online. Please consult with Special Collections staff to request access to this digital content. Note: Special Collections cannot provide access to all file formats due to lack of required software and/or system specifications.
  - De Colores, approximately 2001 (Box 38)
    De Colores (2001) is a 28-minute bilingual documentary about how Latino families are replacing deep roots of homophobia with even deeper roots of love and acceptance. Executive produced by Dee Mosbacher, produced by Peter Barbosa, and co-directed by Peter Barbosa and Garret Lenoir. This file is comprised of audiovisual materials.
  - Radical Harmonies: The Story of Women's Music, 1950-2011
    Radical Harmonies: The Story of Women's Music (2002) is a 90-minute documentary that chronicles the Women's Music Cultural Movement and its evolution from "girl-with-guitar" to a revolution in the roles of women in music and culture. The movement gave birth to an alternative industry that changed women and music forever. Executive produced and directed by Dee Mosbacher; co-produced by Boden Sandstrom; associate produced by Margie Adam; and associate directed by June Millington. This series is comprised of administrative and research records, audiovisual materials, photographs, computer files, and interview files.
    - Administrative: Archival materials, 1999-2001; 2 folders (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
    - Administrative: Articles, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Administrative: Awards and distinctions, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Administrative: Boo shoot, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Administrative: Book, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box 39, Folder 6-8)
    - Administrative: Michigan email, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Administrative: Distribution, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Administrative: Editor search, 2004, 2008; 2 folders (Box 39, Folder 11-12)
    - Administrative: Feedback, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Festivals and Presentations: 26th San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Boston MFA 2004 Screening (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Brasov, Romania Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Chicago, Women in Director Chair, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Cornell Cinema, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Durham North Carolina Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Film festivals notes and miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Gay and Lesbian Film Festival of Brussels, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Festivals and Presentations: GiRL FeST, Honolulu, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Icelandic international gay film festival, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Lesbian Film Festival of Freiburg, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Festivals and Presentations: London (Canada) London Lesbian Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Miscellaneous requests for Radical Harmonies Video/DVD, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Miscellaneous Radical Harmonies screenings, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Festivals and Presentations: New Zealand Reel Queer/Out Takes (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Northampton, Massachusetts Radical Harmonies Concert/Smith College, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Olivia Lesbian Film Festival, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Out-in-Africa, South African GL Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Out Takes Dallas (regarding Out for a Change), 2004 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Portland - Reel Music, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Premiere, 2002; 3 folders (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    - Festivals and Presentation: Presentation by Women In Movement, New Mexico, as part of International Women's Day, Albuquerque, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Reelout--Kingston Queer Film and Video Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Radical Harmonies Festival Schedule, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Radical Harmonies Trafficking Forms, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Spokane GLBT Film Festival, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Taiwan Women Film/Video Festival, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Texas Triangle's Profiles in Pride Series, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Tucson Wingspan LGBT Film Festival, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Western Psychological Association Film Festival, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Withoutabox.com miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Women's Film Festival in Seoul, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Festivals and Presentations: Worldfest Houston International Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Fundraising, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - General, 1994-2004; 2 folders (Box 40, Folder 17-18)
    - Media literature, approximately 2003 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Media People--All videos, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Michigan: crew, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Michigan: General, 1994-1997 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Music: CD project, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Music: General, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Press, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Press kit material, 2003-2005 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
    - Press stills and information, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - Prospectus, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Radical Harmonies, 1994-2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Synopsis, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Treatments, 1997-2001; 4 folders (Box 41, Folder 9-12)
    - Treatments: Research, 1974-2005; 4 folders (Box 41, Folder 13-16)
    - Women's Music Project: Appearance Release Forms, approximately 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Women's Music Project: Biographical Sketches, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Women's Music Project: Flyers, approximately 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Women's Music Project: Miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Women's Music Project: Program description, approximately 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
    - Women's Music Project: Project Resources, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Women's Music Project: BACW 1998/Rad Harmonies (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Women's Music Project: Film Arts Foundation, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Women's Music Project: Outfest, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Women's Music Project: Sundance Film Festival, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Women's Music Project: Prospective Funders, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Women's Music Project: Recommendation Letters: Francis Reid, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Women's Music Project: Recommendation letters: Margie Adam letter, approximately 1998 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Women's Music Project: Rejections, 1996-2004; 3 folders (Box 42, Folder 15-17)
    - Women's Music Project: Shoot-extra material, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Women's Music Project: Thank You Letters, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Film edits: Corrections, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Film edits: February 2003 edit, 2 folders (Box 42, Folder 21-22)
    - Film edits: General, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Film edits: Radical Harmonies corrections, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Michigan Logs, 1997-2006 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Shot logs, 1992-2002; 11 folders (Box 42, Folder 26-29, Box 43, Folder 1-7)
    - Sound bites, approximately 1998-2003 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Transcripts, 1999-2001; 8 folders (Box 43, Folder 9-16)
    - Video tracking: All videos, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Video tracking: 3/4" videos, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Research: General, 1973-1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Research: Margie Adam, 1950-1988 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Research: Ronnie Gilbert, 1973-1981 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Interviews: Supporting materials, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1999-2002; 22 folders (Box 44, Folder 5-10, Box 45, Folder 1-16)
    - History of women's music audiovisual materials, approximately 1992-2003; 4 boxes (Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49)
    - Audiovisual materials and film documentation, 1975-2011; 15 boxes (Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63)
    - Digital images and documentation for Radical Harmonies, 2001-2002; 17.5 Gigabytes (48 ISO disc images from 48 data CDs)
      This digital content is not currently available online; please consult with Special Collections staff to request access. Note that Special Collections may not be able to provide required software for some file formats.
    - Radical Harmonies computer files, 2002-2003; 129.08 Gigabytes (5,064 digital files copied from 1 hard drive)
      Video production files for Radical Harmonies
    - Radical Harmonies computer files (Dee's FW Drive), 2007-2008; 70 Gigabytes (4,664 digital files copied from 1 hard drive)
      Note that Special Collections may not be able to provide required software for some file formats.
  - No Secret Anymore, 2000-2004
    No Secret Anymore (2003) is a 57-minute documentary that follows lesbian icons and founders of the Daughters of Bilitis—Del Martin and Phyllis Lyon—through six decades from the fear of discovery to the expectation of equality. Produced, written, and directed by Joan E. Biren (JEB); produced by Dee Mosbacher; associate produced by Margie Adam and Jason Heffner; co-produced by Woman Vision and Moonforce Media. This series is comprised of administrative records, photographs, resources, and audiovisual materials.
    - Administrative: Castro Theatre Rental Info, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Administrative: No Secret Anymore Premiere, Castro, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: del and Phyll NCLR shoot, approximately 2000-2004; 2 folders (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
    - Photographs: Phyll. birthday, approximately 2000-2004 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Resources, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
    - Audiovisual materials, 1994-1999 (Box 65)
  - Training Rules
    Training Rules (2008) is a 60-minute documentary that examines how women's collegiate sports, caught in a web of homophobic practices at Penn State University, colludes in the destruction of the lives and dreams of its most talented athletes. Co-produced and directed by Dee Mosbacher and Fawn Yacker. This series is comprised of administrative and financial records, photographs, planning and production records, computer files, and audiovisual materials.
    - Administrative: Articles, 1986-2010; 8 folders (Box 66, Folder 1-8)
    - Administrative: Ben Schofield's notebook, 2007; 2 folders (Box 66, Folder 9-10)
    - Administrative: Clearances, General information, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Administrative: Copyright registration, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Administrative: Dee, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Administrative: Distribution, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Administrative: ESPN, 2008-2009 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Administrative: Fair use/Al Wickens, 2006-2009 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Administrative: Fair use in film/See RC version ITVS phase III, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Agape Foundation, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Finishing funds, undated, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Frameline extra material, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Grants for Training Rules, 2008; 6 folders (Box 66, Folder 21-26)
    - Financial: Horizon's Foundation, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - General Training Rules materials, 2007; 2 folders (Box 67, Folder 2-3)
    - Jen shoot, 2007-2008 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - NYC - October 2008, 2006-2008 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Orlando shoot, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Penn State University team photographs, scans, and invoices, 1981-2009; 7 folders (Box 67, Folder 8-14)
    - Publicity, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Release form prototype, undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Releases, NYC, 1986-2005 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Shoot, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Shoot: Esera T, Andrea, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Production files: 1991 protest footage, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Production files: Air travel, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Production files: Alma mater information, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Production files: Atlanta Film Festival, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Production files: B-Roll materials, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Production files: Car rental, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Production files: Centre court media purchase, approximately 2007 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Production files: Center court log notes, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Production files: Chicago Sun Times, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Production files: Cindy's games, approximately 2007 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Production files: Communications, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Production files: Contact information, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Production files: Diana Nyad narration with transcript, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Production files: Edit notes, 2007-2009; 4 folders (Box 68, Folder 1-4)
    - Production files: Editor lists, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Production files: Equipment/purchase rental and press release/samples, 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Production files: Festival information, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Production files: Frameline, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Production files: Frameline application, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Production files: Grant writing tips, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Production files: Graphics, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Production files: Graphics/after effects, Gina's list, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Production files: Historic newspaper archives, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Production files: Hotel/lodging, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Production files: In use/Not found in H drive/old notes, 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Production files: Intern ad-bavc, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 1 proposal, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 1 work copies, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 1 budget, 2005-2007 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 1 copies, approximately 2007 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 2 feedback, approximately 2007 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 3 guidelines, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 3 older copy, approximately 2007 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Production files for ITVS: Phase 3 final copies, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Production files: Lisa Faloon letter to Rene, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Production files: Location shots/Ashley Esterline, approximately 2005-2007 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Production files: Log PSU vs. George Washington, Courtney Wicks, approximately 2007 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Production files: Logo-100/500, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Production files: Media requests, 2006-2007 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Production files: Miami Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Mills Colleges shoot: TR recreations 11/14/08, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Mills Colleges shoot: Audio and shot list, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Mills Colleges shoot: Call sheet, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Mills Colleges shoot: Head shots, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Mills Colleges shoot: Mills information, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Production files: Music, approximately 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Production files: Music log, approximately 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Production files: Narration, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Production files: Narrations-transcriptions, work copies, 2008; 2 folders (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Production files: NCLR-list, approximately 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Production files: Old/to do, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Production files: Philadelphia Film Festival, 2008-2009 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Production files: Players schedules, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Production files: Portfolio database, approximately 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Production files: Publicist, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Production files: Rene/Mighty Macs/Immaculata, Bio, Title Nine, etc., 2008 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Production files for rough cut: Questionnaire, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Production files for rough cut: Questions-draft, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Production files for rough cut: Notes, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Production files for rough cut: June 2008/TR responses (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Production files for rough cut: Responses, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Production files for rough cut: Questions, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Production files for rough cut: January 21, 23, 26, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Production files for rough cut: Fawn/rough cut feedback from emails, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Production files for rough cut: Screening on April 9, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Production files for rough cut: 8/21/08 invites, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Production files for rough cut: Invites/screening rooms, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Production files: Script, 2008 March 18; 2 folders (Box 69, Folder 21-22)
    - Production files: Scripts, old, 2007-2008; 5 folders (Box 69, Folder 23-27)
    - Production files: Shot list/PSU Old, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Production files: Shot list-TR, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Production files: Skype, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Production files: Sports footage, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Production files: Structure, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Production files: Sue Rankin-story possible string out, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Production files: Synopsis (3 versions), approximately 2007-2008 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Production files: Time line, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Production files: Tampa shoot, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Production files: Transcription-TR, 2007-2008; 2 folders (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
    - Production files: Transcripts of script, old, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Production files: Treatments/old, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Production files: Video arts/on-line, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Production files: Voice over, approximately 2008 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Production files: Web design/TR, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Production files: Wolfe distribution, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Website, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Film files: Back-up cast for 12/5/08, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Film files: B-roll needed, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Film files: Call sheet 12/5/08, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Film files: Cast for 12/5/08, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Film files: Center Court video - in use, RC, 2007-2008 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Film files: Editors, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Film files: Editor's notes and transcripts, 2005-2008; 3 folders (Box 70, Folder 25-27)
    - Film files: ESPN - in use video, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Film festivals: Festival miscellaneous, 2010 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Film festivals: General, 2009; 4 folders (Box 70, Folder 30-33)
    - Film festivals: Guest passes, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Film files: Gina Leibrecht/editor contact, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Film files: In Use w/ Thumbnails, 2008; 4 folders (Box 71, Folder 3-6)
    - Film files: Jen's game footage/pearl dubs, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Film files: Latest in-use document, 2009; 3 folders (Box 71, Folder 8-11)
    - Film files: Miscellaneous, approximately 2007-2009 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Film files: News footage in use, 2007 December 1 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Film files: Photos from article in use, RC, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Film files: PSU video in use (No Center Court), 2007 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Film files: PSU photos/may or may not be PSU in use, 2008 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Film files: Production list, approximately 2007-2008 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Film files: Recreation scripts, approximately 2007-2008 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Film files: Screenings, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Film files: Training rules status report, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Film transcripts: Ron - NCAA: T2, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Film transcripts, 2007; 51 folders (51 folders in 6 boxes) (Box 71, Folder 22-26, Box 72, Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Folder 1-2)
    - Film files: Video in use (no Center court), rough cut, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Film files: video - Jen's home movies, in use, RC, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Notes, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Notes: Center Court notes, 2003-2005 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Notes: Collegiate Images, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Notes: Completion to dos, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Notes: CSTV/CBS College Sports, 2006-2008 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Notes: General, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Notes: Indiana (PA) Gazette, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Notes: Various Correspondence, approximately 2007-2009; 2 folders (Box 76, Folder 11, Folder 15)
    - Notes: "In-coming media" media requests log sheet, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Notes: Needs attention, approximately 2007-2009 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Notes: Articles/photos, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Notes: Website needs, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Notes: Michigan vs PSU protests, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Notes: Searched, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Notes: Though equity *liability game/Joe Paterno AD, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Notes: Training Rules, 2007-2009 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Notes: WPSX/WPSU, 2006-2008 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Research: 2006 protest, 2006-2007 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Research: Julie Byrne, O God of Players: The Story of the Immaculatata Mighty Macs, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Research: Chicago Sun Times clearance info, approximately 2006-2009 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Research: Civil Action document, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Research: Courtney Wicks, approximately 2006-2008 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Research: Flat art to be filmed, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Research: Flat art shoot, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Research: Jen lawsuit papers, approximately 2006-2008 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Research: Lisa Faloon letter, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Research: Martina Fund (Women's Sports Foundation - homophobia and sports), 2001 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Research: Merry Stephens, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Research: Miscellaneous, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Research: NCLR letter to Spanier, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Research: National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR) materials, approximately 2005-2006; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 10-11)
    - Research: NCLR press release, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Research: NCLR press release/files lawsuit, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 13)